Linda Donahue Collection of Labor and Leftist Publications 6357 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Linda Donahue Collection of Labor and Leftist Publications
1906-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Donahue, Linda
6357 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Pamphlets, journal issues, publications, photographs.
8056618
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 30, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8056618
- The Case of Sacco and Vanzetti in Cartoons From the Daily Worker, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Continental Walk, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes and Resolutions of the Continental Congress of Workers and Farmers for Economic Reconstruction, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New Masses, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- New Masses, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- New Masses, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Origins of Left Culture in the U.S., 1880-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Present Day Socialism, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Red Cartoons, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Red Cartoons, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Red Number of Judge, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Song Books, 1935-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Socialist Review, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Think or Surrender, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Unemployed, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Unfinished Revolution, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- May Day Photographs (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Multiple photocopies of four photographs of May Day parades. No originals.